John J. Sirica Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Classified, 1973 (Box CL 1)
  - United States District Court File (Box CL 1)
    - Case File
      - Watergate cases
        - Cases
          - United States v. Liddy
            - Presentencing file, 1973
        - Miscellaneous
          - United States Senate
            - Committee on Appropriations, Central Intelligence Agency hearings, 1973
            - Committee on Armed Services, Central Intelligence Agency hearings, 1973